ILGWU 4x5 Negatives of Photographs 5780 P N45
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Australian visitor L. Short Secretary Of Federation of Ironworkers of Australia with H. Haskel. 1954. (item no.151) (Box 13, Folder 151)
- South American visitors with Luigi Antonini. School graduation on a field trip with Serafini Romualdi. Puerto Rico. Mexico. Salvadore. Colombia and Costa Rica. 2/20/54. (item no.152), 1954 (Box 13, Folder 152)
- Canadian group from Montreal visit Health Center. 1/12/1954. (item no.153) (Box 13, Folder 153)
  February 12th (4P and 6N)
- Peruvian visitors at Local 22, Nehama-Zimmerman 3/9/1954. (item no.154) (Box 13, Folder 154)
  March 9th (P and N)
- Japanese visitors at International Ladies Garment with Mark Starr. 1/24/55. (item no.155), 1955 (Box 13, Folder 155)
  January 24th (P and N)
- Martino, Gaetano (Italian Foreign Minister) with Antonini and Ferraris Carlo, 4/1/55 (item no.156), 1955 (Box 13, Folder 156)
  April 1st (P and N)
- Cuban Hotel-Restaurant delegation visits local 22 Zimmerman. 5/18/55. (item no.157), 1955 (Box 13, Folder 157)
  May 18th (P and N)
- Belgian visitors at International Ladies Garment lectured by Stein & Crone. 2/1/55. (item no.158), 1955 (Box 13, Folder 158)
  February 1st (P and N)
- Reisel, Victor in New York Mirror with Dubinsky and Fred Woltman (item no.159) (Box 13, Folder 159)
  (4P and 2N)
- Woll, Matthew and Antonini at 75th Birthday Testimonial, 1/8/55 (item no.160), 1955 (Box 13, Folder 160)
  January 8th (P and N)
- Stewart, Michael lecturing at Unity House 6/11/54 (item no.161), 1954 (Box 13, Folder 161)
  June 11th (P and N)
- Flood, Dan (Pennsylvania Congressman) 1954 (item no.162) (Box 13, Folder 162)
- Bowles, Chester, lecture at Local 38, 10/31/55 (item no.163), 1955 (Box 13, Folder 163)
  October 31st (P and N)
- Taft at training institute, 7/29/55 (item no.164), 1955 (Box 13, Folder 164)
  July 29th (P and 2N)
- Executive Council AFL.-CIO. At Unity House. 1958 (item no.165) (Box 13, Folder 165)
- Latin America visitors with Fannia Cohn. 1955. (item no.166) (Box 13, Folder 166)
- President of Italy tours Garment Center. Luncheon at Waldorf Astoria 1956. (item no.167) (Box 13, Folder 167)
  (4P and 6N)
- Wagner, Robert Jr. with Dubinsky, Antonini at Italian American Labor Council, 12/55 (item no.168), 1955 (Box 13, Folder 168)
  December (2P and N)
- Zimmerman, Charles sworn in as member of Mayors Commission of Inter-Group Relations (item no.169) (Box 13, Folder 169)
- Roosevelt, Eleanor at mike at AFL-CIO convention, 1955 (item no.170) (Box 13, Folder 170)
- Trigeres Fashion Show. Full Collection July 1956 (item no.171) (Box 13, Folder 171)
  July (13P and 14N)
- Operators- men at sewing machines. A. Goodman Shop. 1951 (item no.172) (Box 13, Folder 172)
- Morrow at sewing machine. Local 105 (P) (item no.173) (Box 13, Folder 173)
- Women operators at a large factory. Local 62 (P) (item no.174) (Box 13, Folder 174)
- Button Hole Maker (P) (item no.175) (Box 13, Folder 175)
- Hand finishing. Girls. 2 negatives (P) (item no.176) (Box 13, Folder 176)
- Operators of Local 62 undergarments (P) (item no.177) (Box 13, Folder 177)
- Male presser. Hoffman presser (P) (item no.178) (Box 13, Folder 178)
- Men working at knitting machines 3/22/53 (P) (item no.179), 1953 (Box 13, Folder 179)
  March 22nd (P and N)
- Woman cleaning dresses. Puerto Ricans. 6/25/53 (P) (item no.180), 1953 (Box 13, Folder 180)
  June 25th
- Skirts stockroom (item no.181) (Box 13, Folder 181)
  (2P and 2N) Missing
- Mboya, Tom General Secretary of Kenyas Federation of Labor at Training Institute, 1956 (item no.182) (Box 13, Folder 182)
- Preparing and behind the scenes at George Carmel Incorporated and Zelinka-Matlick. June 1958 (item no.183) (Box 13, Folder 183)
  June (38P and 18N)
- Japanese Trade Unionists with Maida Springer. 9/56. (item no.184), 1956 (Box 13, Folder 184)
  September (P and N)
- Mexican Trade Unionists with Charles Zimmerman. 1956. (item no.185) (Box 13, Folder 185)
  (P and 2N)
- Latin American Trade Unionists Training group with Reina. 10/56 (item no.186), 1956 (Box 13, Folder 186)
- Italian Trade Unionists visit International Ladies Garment. 10/56. (item no.187), 1956 (Box 13, Folder 187)
  October (P and N)
- Kethley, Ann (Former Minister of the Hungarian Government), 12/56 (item no.188), 1956 (Box 13, Folder 188)
- Hands (item no.189) (Box 13, Folder 189)
  (23N)
- Puerto Rico Houses Santiago Iglesias, Dubinsky Breaking Ground for. Houses (item no.190), 1957 (Box 13, Folder 190)
  May 16th (3P and 3N)
- Montana, Vanni decorated as official Knight of the Italian Republic, 4/20/56 (item no.191), 1956 (Box 13, Folder 191)
  April 20th (2P and 2N)
- Crone, Harry honored by the Newspaper Guild, 6/50 (item no.192), 1950 (Box 13, Folder 192)
  June (5P and 7N)
- Kreindler, Charles gets Touch of Hope Award, 12/13/56 (item no.193), 1956 (Box 13, Folder 193)
  December 13th (2P and 4N)
- Wagner, Robert Jr. at Shulimskys shop, 38th St. and 7th Ave., with Appleton, 10/56 (item no.194), 1956 (Box 13, Folder 194)
- Wagner, Robert Jr. as guest speaker at mike at Local 22 meeting, 10/56 (item no.1), 1956 (Box 14, Folder 1)
- Groundbreaking for the Fashion Institute of Technology. 8/30/1956 (item no.2) (Box 14, Folder 2)
  August 30th
- Lehman receiving AFL-CIO Community Services Murray-Green Award, 12/11/56 (item no.3), 1956 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  December 11th
- Indonesian Emissary Representative Minister of Labor to study labor in USA. 6/29/1956 (item no.4) (Box 14, Folder 4)
  June 29th
- Lima, Peru Secretary of Textile Workers Union Ramon S. Reano & Zimmerman. 9/10/57 (item no.5), 1957 (Box 14, Folder 5)
- Nigeria visitors with Stein and Springer July 1957. (item no.6) (Box 14, Folder 6)
- Kovler, Morris speaking, 9/19/57 (item no.7) (Box 14, Folder 7)
  September 19th
- Roosevelt, Eleanor with Zimmerman at Liberal Party meeting, 9/25/1956 (item no.8) (Box 14, Folder 8)
  September 25th
- Stulberg & Mrs. Stulberg at a birthday party, 4/14/56 (item no.9), 1956 (Box 14, Folder 9)
- Stulberg honored by Local 62; Falikman & Kreinder, 5/22/56 (item no.10), 1956 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  May 22nd
- Stulberg with Martin Rose 12/14/57 (item no.11), 1957 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  December 14st
- Stulberg with Dubinsky, Potofsky, and Meany, 12/21/57 (item no.12), 1957 (Box 14, Folder 12)
- Stulberg with Zimmerman at Zimmermans 60th Birthday Party, 11/23/57 (item no.13), 1957 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  January 23rd
- Kessler at mike, 12/14/54 (item no.14), 1954 (Box 14, Folder 14)
- Zimmerman, Charles with Costa Rican visitors, 12/3/57 (item no.15), 1957 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  December 3rd
- Hochman with Pins and Needles actors, 12/20/57 (item no.16), 1957 (Box 14, Folder 16)
- Kaye, Jack with Mark Starr, 10/22/57 (item no.17), 1957 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  October 22nd
- Davidson, Ben with Robert Wagner and Reiss, 10/31/57 (item no.18), 1957 (Box 14, Folder 18)
  October 31st
- Nelson, Louis at National Shorecroppers Fund Meeting, 11/13/57 (item no.19), 1957 (Box 14, Folder 19)
  November 13th
- Harriman, Averel Gov. and Fred Waltman at Zimmermans 60th Birthday, 11/27/57 (item no.20), 1957 (Box 14, Folder 20)
  January 27th
- Randolph, Philip A. at a AFL-CIO conference, 11/13/57 (item no.21), 1957 (Box 14, Folder 21)
- Perlman, Selig Professor with Dr. Lawrence Bethel at Feinberg Memorial, 10/8/1957 (item no.22) (Box 14, Folder 22)
  October 8th
- Dubinsky points to enlarged PPR forms at Local 10, 7/17/57 (item no.23), 1957 (Box 14, Folder 23)
  July 17th
- Hayes, Paul with Dubinsky and Alex Rose, 7/10/57 (item no.24), 1957 (Box 14, Folder 24)
  July 10th
- Sicilian visitors at restaurant and Station WEVD. 2/16/57. (item no.25), 1957 (Box 14, Folder 25)
  February 16th
- Korean visitors examine a garment. 4/2/57. (item no.26), 1957 (Box 14, Folder 26)
  April 2nd
- Alessi, Giuseppe (from Sicily) with Paul Tommarchi Chair Building Director of Plastic Arts Corporation, Montana. 3/12/57 (item no.27), 1957 (Box 14, Folder 27)
  March 12th
- Haskell, Hannah; mother and father in Florida, 5/57 (item no.28), 1957 (Box 14, Folder 28)
- Tonn, Alex at his desk (item no.29) (Box 14, Folder 29)
- James B. Corey and Martin Luther King at Social Justice Award Astor Hotel 4/24/57 (item no.30), 1957 (Box 14, Folder 30)
- Zimmerman, Charles giving L.I.D. Award to Senor Fernando Sierra Berdecia for Govenor Louis Munoz Marin of Puerto Rico at luncheon at Waldorf Astoria, 4/13/57 (item no.31), 1957 (Box 14, Folder 31)
  April 13th
- Zimmerman, Charles at Local 22 graduation at High Sschool of Fashion Industries, 22 W.24thth St., with Govenor Harriman, Dr. Leo Ritter and others, 6/19/57 (item no.32) (Box 14, Folder 32)
- Schoenwald, Mat. pointing to enlarged P.P.R. poster in Local 62 files, 3/14/57 (item no.33), 1957 (Box 14, Folder 33)
  July 14th
- Stulberg honored by New York County Liberal Party, 3/17/57 (item no.34), 1957 (Box 14, Folder 34)
  May 17th
- Stulberg at Liberal Partys Anniversary Dinner with Dubinsky, Harriman, Alex Rose, and Wagner, 6/19/57 (item no.35) (Box 14, Folder 35)
- Galbraith, John K. Dr. Harvard Universit) portrait with his hands at his face ,4/18/53, and one speaking Starr looking on, 11/21/57 (item no.36), 1957 (Box 14, Folder 36)
  April 18th and November 21st
- Meany, George gets Freedom Award Antonini and Harriman, 1957 (item no.37) (Box 14, Folder 37)
- 3 generations of pressers (P) 1957 (item no.38) (Box 14, Folder 38)
- David Dubinsky at press conference about old age home, 2/26/57 (item no.39), 1957 (Box 14, Folder 39)
  February 26th
- Nevada Mortgage Contract. 5/1/57 (item no.40), 1957 (Box 14, Folder 40)
  May 1st
- Bunche, Ralph Dr. with Dr. Kuame Nkrumch of Ghana, Ph. Randolph and Mrs. Bunche (item no.41) (Box 14, Folder 41)
- Lehmans 80th Birthday Party by Liberal Party, 3/29/58 (item no.42), 1958 (Box 14, Folder 42)
- Stluberg making a tape with Starr, 2/14/58 (item no.43), 1958 (Box 14, Folder 43)
  February 14th
- Stulberg with Bernard Shane and 2 Canadian employers in Miami Beach, 1958 (item no.44) (Box 14, Folder 44)
- Roosevelt, Eleanor with students of Womens Trade Union League, 6/6/1958 (item no.45) (Box 14, Folder 45)
  June 6th
- French West African visitors with Starr and Ionenko. April 29,1958. (item no.46) (Box 14, Folder 46)
  April 29th
- Japanese visitors. Mrs. Harabayashi-novelist with Stein. 5/29/1958. (item no.47) (Box 14, Folder 47)
  May 29th
- African editor of Labor Papers with Stein. 4/23/58. (item no.48), 1958 (Box 14, Folder 48)
  April 23rd
- German head of textile and garment union- Werner Bock, David Dubinsky and Charles Kreindler. 6/5/1958. (item no.49) (Box 14, Folder 49)
  June 5th
- Argentina Labor visitors with David Dubinsky. 3/3/58. (item no.50), 1958 (Box 14, Folder 50)
  March 3rd
- Visitors from West Europe with Helen- Education Department. 4/24/1958. (item no.51) (Box 14, Folder 51)
- Zimmerman, Charles and Harry Fox, 11/6/58 (item no.52), 1958 (Box 14, Folder 52)
  November 6th
- Swedish Trade Union Delegation visits David Dubinsky. 11/3/58. (item no.53), 1958 (Box 14, Folder 53)
  November 3rd
- Mendelsund, Henoch portrait, copy negative, 1959 (item no.54) (Box 14, Folder 54)
- Goldenberg, Max at work 1/21/59 (item no.55), 1959 (Box 14, Folder 55)
  January 21st
- Pokodner, Herbert at work with an interracial group discussion, 1/22/1959 (item no.56) (Box 14, Folder 56)
- Quintilliano, Louis, new manager at work (Local 38), 1/23/59 (item no.57), 1959 (Box 14, Folder 57)
- Four Fredoms Award to Harry Truman Dec. 5, 1959 (item no.58) (Box 14, Folder 58)
  December 5th
- Japanese guests- Labor Management teams with Dr. Reuter. 11/23/59 (item no.59), 1959 (Box 14, Folder 59)
  November 23rd
- Swedish delegation with Stulberg and Hochman in Council room. 10/20/59. (item no.60), 1959 (Box 14, Folder 60)
- Chilean Delegation with Rubin and Teper. 10/22/59 (item no.61), 1959 (Box 14, Folder 61)
  OPctober 22nd
- Mendelsund, Henoch election and installation at Coak Joint Board Headquarters, 9/30/59 (item no.62), 1959 (Box 14, Folder 62)
  September 30th
- Stulberg at a Liberal Partys dinner with Humphrey, Dubinsky, Zimmerman, and others, 5/59 (item no.63), 1959 (Box 14, Folder 63)
- Award at the New School for Lichtenstein with (12/11/53) Held (12/53) (P) (item no.64), 1953 (Box 14, Folder 64)
  December 11th- 12th
- National Committee For labor Israel Conference, Stulberg chairman 11/28/59 (P) (item no.65), 1959 (Box 14, Folder 65)
  November 28th
- Histadruts Humanitarina Award to Potofsky & David Dubinsky.6/23/59 (item no.66), 1959 (Box 14, Folder 66)
- Dedication of Women Greens Library. Held, Zimmerman, Potofsky, David Dubinsky. Meany 4/20/59 (item no.67), 1959 (Box 14, Folder 67)
- Starr, Mark with Stulberg & Potofsky at luncheon for Starr, 12/10/59 (item no.68), 1959 (Box 14, Folder 68)
- Zimmerman, Charles and Abe Schrader interviewed by National Broadcasting Company, 3/18/59 (item no.69), 1959 (Box 14, Folder 69)
  May 18th
- 4 Workers give blood for a coworker at B & O Dress Company. 2/11/59. (item no.70), 1959 (Box 14, Folder 70)
- Man at a special machine May 1959 (P) (item no.71) (Box 14, Folder 71)
- Bagno, Morris resumes work back from retirement, 9/59 (item no.72), 1959 (Box 14, Folder 72)
- Antonini, With Mayor Wagner, Polio Citation, 6/30/59 (item no.73), 1959 (Box 14, Folder 73)
  June 30th
- United Italian American Labor Council common. Hotel 12/20/58 (item no.74), 1958 (Box 14, Folder 74)
- National Urban League Award Equal Opportunity Days with Meany, David Dubinsky. Lee Bristol, General Sarnoff & Ph. Randolph 11/17/59 (item no.75), 1959 (Box 14, Folder 75)
- Kayser Roth strike. General Executive board on line 6/2/58 (item no.76), 1958 (Box 14, Folder 76)
- 1 day strike local 60A 1/12/54 (item no.77), 1954 (Box 14, Folder 77)
  January 12th
- Mass demonstration, Pennsylvania jobbers in New York 8/26/58 (P) (item no.78), 1958 (Box 14, Folder 78)
  August 26th
- Pennsylvania in New York Budget Dress Corporation 462 7th Avenue 5/28/58 (P) (item no.79), 1958 (Box 14, Folder 79)
  May 28th
- Strike G.H.&E. Freydberg Showroom, 1359 Broadway 5/6/54. (item no.80), 1954 (Box 14, Folder 80)
- Strike Pickets Budget Dress 462 7th Avenue 1958 (item no.81) (Box 14, Folder 81)
- Hands cutting a pile of mat. Copy negative. Cover New York Times (P) (item no.82) (Box 14, Folder 82)
- Jack Di Marco, presser Local 48; 22 years in same shop 2/59 (P0 (item no.83), 1959 (Box 14, Folder 83)
- Dutch delegation ECA visits the International Ladies Garment. 1949. (item no.84), 1959 (Box 14, Folder 84)
- Japanese Industrialists in WFDR station sponsored tour of America. 7/10/1950. (item no.85) (Box 14, Folder 85)
- Japanese visitors in the Council Room. January 1956. (item no.86) (Box 14, Folder 86)
- German Trade Unionists visit ORT. 1948. (item no.87) (Box 14, Folder 87)
- Greek Trade Unionists with Wilbur Daniels. 2/5/51. (item no.88), 1951 (Box 14, Folder 88)
  February 5th
- Austrian Labor Editors with Danish. 2/15/51. (item no.89), 1951 (Box 14, Folder 89)
  February 15th
- Belgian ECA Team visits International Ladies Garment WFDR radio station 7/17 (item no.90), 1917 (Box 14, Folder 90)
- Danish delegation visits International Ladies Garment. 2/21/51. (item no.91), 1951 (Box 14, Folder 91)
  February 21st
- German heads of trade unions- G. Reuter, Peter Keller and Dr. Tepper. (item no.92) (Box 14, Folder 92)
- Japanese visitors with Starr. 4/13/51. (item no.93), 1951 (Box 14, Folder 93)
- South American visitors to Educational Department. 9/51 (item no.94), 1951 (Box 14, Folder 94)
- Roosevelt, Eleanor with French ECA, 12/2/50 (item no.95), 1950 (Box 14, Folder 95)
  February 2nd
- Lovestone, Jay with Meany,9/24/57 (item no.96), 1957 (Box 14, Folder 96)
  September 24th
- Local 25, 1913. Ex Board Ladies Waist and Dressmakers Union (item no.97) (Box 14, Folder 97)
- Early minutes written by hand of meeting (item no.98) (Box 14, Folder 98)
- Unidentified. Conference (item no.99) (Box 14, Folder 99)
- Woodcut from Wood cuts U.S.A 2 ladies garment workers (item no.100) (Box 14, Folder 100)
- Executive Board, Cloak Local 9, 1915 (item no.101) (Box 14, Folder 101)
- Strike leaders of Cleveland Dr. and Cl Kreindler, Julius Hochman, etc (item no.102) (Box 14, Folder 102)
- Mayor London and Senator Lehman playing chess (item no.103) (Box 14, Folder 103)
- Roosevelt and Lehman and others (item no.104) (Box 14, Folder 104)
- General Executive Board Union Card 1890 (item no.105) (Box 14, Folder 105)
- Story on workers complaint. Griefs settled on the job. Local 99, November 29,1957 (item no.106) (Box 14, Folder 106)
  40876
- Garment Center watches Ball Game October 1957 (P) (item no.107) (Box 14, Folder 107)
- Designer at work. Woman with sketches of dresses in hands (P) 1957 (item no.108) (Box 14, Folder 108)
- 2 girls buying clothes 2/25/1954 (item no.109) (Box 14, Folder 109)
  February 25th
- Woman operator sewing petticoats 7/1954 (P) (item no.110) (Box 14, Folder 110)
- Hot weather operator Ginger Frocks 329 W 39th Street, 7/23/57 (item no.111), 1957 (Box 14, Folder 111)
- Women operators in a Baltimore factory. 7/1958 (item no.112) (Box 14, Folder 112)
- Women, Men packing garments July 1955 Local 99 (P) (item no.113) (Box 14, Folder 113)
- Childrens Fashion Show 1955 (item no.114) (Box 14, Folder 114)
- Women and Men workers at machines, A. Goodman Dress Shop 1951 (P) (item no.115) (Box 14, Folder 115)
- Cutter of Local 10 Ale Berner stretching mat. Oct. 1957 (P) (item no.116) (Box 14, Folder 116)
- Chairman Dave Weber takes care of workers problem in shop November 1958 (P) (item no.117) (Box 14, Folder 117)
- Chairlady and Committee adjust price in shop 4, 4/5/57. (P) (item no.118), 1957 (Box 14, Folder 118)
- Cotton Art Mills. B. Stoller 630 Broadway 8/9/57 (P) (item no.119), 1957 (Box 14, Folder 119)
  August 9th
- Sample hand of A. Goodman shop October 1951 (P) (item no.120) (Box 14, Folder 120)
- Men. Cloak Shop Operator. Marquise 512-7 Ave. 4/14/59 (item no.121), 1959 (Box 14, Folder 121)
- Operators at machines. Merr and Women 1951 (P) (item no.122) (Box 14, Folder 122)
- Woman standing at a button marking machine 3/22/53 (P) (item no.123), 1953 (Box 14, Folder 123)
  March 22nd
- Finishers, men and women cloak shop Morguise 4/14/1959 (P) (item no.124) (Box 14, Folder 124)
- Photo of a Singer machine with chair, no worker (item no.125) (Box 14, Folder 125)
- Man with a hand truck, Union label on it (P) (item no.126) (Box 14, Folder 126)
- Booklet on Industrial Crafts Local 105 (item no.127) (Box 14, Folder 127)
- Luncheon Commodore Hotel, Patore, Brosio, Wagner, Antonini David Dubinsky. December,17 1955 (item no.128) (Box 14, Folder 128)
  December 17th
- Italian American. Labor Council .Local 89 12/15/53 (item no.129), 1953 (Box 14, Folder 129)
  December 15th
- Testimonial to Giulio Pastore Commodore Hotel Meany, Reuter 12/4/52 (P) (item no.130), 1952 (Box 14, Folder 130)
  December 4th
- Brown, Irving at the Annual Meeting of the Italian-American Labor Council, 12/12/52 (item no.131), 1952 (Box 14, Folder 131)
  December 12th
- Council receives $2500 from Nat Borskin of Popular Dress Manufacturing 1/11/56 (item no.132), 1956 (Box 14, Folder 132)
  January 11th
- Poster of With These Hands on channel 4. March 1, 52 (item no.133), 1952 (Box 14, Folder 133)
  40603
- David Dubinsky. Newfound family in Europe 1957 (item no.134) (Box 14, Folder 134)
- Gulag Slavery map copy for Lovestone 3/13/53. (item no.135), 1953 (Box 14, Folder 135)
  March 13th
- China portraits copy for Lovestone. 3/53. (item no.136), 1953 (Box 14, Folder 136)
- Copy for Lovestone General Marshal with Red Communists Leaders. 9/1953. (item no.137) (Box 14, Folder 137)
- Picketing Russian Consulate for Anti-Jewish Acts. 1/23/1953. (item no.138) (Box 14, Folder 138)
- Wood cutters & Gus Durham Bulldozers. 7/121953. (item no.139) (Box 14, Folder 139)
  July 12th
- Dolls dressed by workers for charity sale. November 11/24/1954. (item no.140) (Box 14, Folder 140)
  November 24th
- New York Photo Engraving Union 853 Broadway Henry Bankoff. 4/22/1954. (item no.141) (Box 14, Folder 141)
  April 22nd
- Local 105 Photo of Childrens clothes. March 1954. (item no.142) (Box 14, Folder 142)
- Drill Press at Burndy for State Department Job, 1954. (item no.143) (Box 14, Folder 143)
- Nigerian Art & Cultural Exhibit at Carnegie Endowment Center 4/19/55 (item no.144) (Box 14, Folder 144)
- A.F.L.-C.I.O. gift for Genewa Murals 10/25/55. (item no.145), 1955 (Box 14, Folder 145)
  October 25th
- Hats & Coats on rack Conference in Council Room. 1955. (item no.146) (Box 14, Folder 146)
- Union Maid. 1957. (item no.147) (Box 14, Folder 147)
- Dues machines and dues being paid at Union headquarters. 1958. (item no.148) (Box 14, Folder 148)
- Sweepstake winner $140,000 Est. Cruz. June 5, 1958. (item no.149) (Box 14, Folder 149)
- Clerk at window. Workers outside. 1958. (item no.150) (Box 14, Folder 150)
- Historic undergarment modeled by local 62 members Union Hall. 9/11/59. (item no.151), 1959 (Box 14, Folder 151)
  September 11th
- Labor Day sign at 7th Ave. August 19, 1959. (item no.152) (Box 14, Folder 152)
  August 19th
- Copy for Stulberg.3/59 (item no.153), 1959 (Box 14, Folder 153)
- Pictures of globe (item no.154) (Box 14, Folder 154)
- American Heart Association University Hospital. (item no.155) (Box 14, Folder 155)
- Rockefeller Plaza Radio City. (item no.156) (Box 14, Folder 156)
- Newsreel Cameramen lined up. (item no.157) (Box 14, Folder 157)
- 3 Union Books with stamps. (item no.158) (Box 14, Folder 158)
- Fire Sprinkler. (item no.159) (Box 14, Folder 159)
- Operator of Hat Union at machine. (item no.160) (Box 14, Folder 160)
- Statue of Liberty. (item no.161) (Box 14, Folder 161)
- Types. 4 people 9/1957. (P) (item no.162) (Box 14, Folder 162)
- Little International. 3 women, African American, Chinese, and White. (P). (item no.163) (Box 14, Folder 163)
- Medical baby is born-operation. (item no.164) (Box 14, Folder 164)
- Haywood Broun Memorial; Newspaper Guild contract signing; Morning Telegraphy Triangle Publication, 12/5/1952 (item no.165) (Box 14, Folder 165)
- Haywood Broun Memorial; presentation of portrait to Joe Collis, 11/15/54 (item no.166), 1954 (Box 14, Folder 166)
- Thomas, Normans 75th Birthday Dinner given by his friends, 11/19/59 (item no.167) (Box 14, Folder 167)
- Picket line in front of Seampruf-Slips in Scranton (P) 4/1951 (item no.168) (Box 14, Folder 168)
- Dress strike P&F 642 So Boulevard 6/7/1951 (P) (item no.169) (Box 14, Folder 169)
- Sarah Ozaria Dress Strike June 7, 1951 (item no.170) (Box 14, Folder 170)
- Local 155 helps Wisconsin strike against Marinette Knit Mills June 13, 1951 (item no.171) (Box 14, Folder 171)
  June 13th
- Cloak strike against racketeers open shops August 8/6/1952 (P) (item no.172) (Box 14, Folder 172)
  August 6th
- Cloak strike Nagler, Kaplan, Hyman, pickets on 38th Street August 8/6/1952. (item no.173) (Box 14, Folder 173)
- Dress organization strike May 28, 1952 (P) (item no.174) (Box 14, Folder 174)
- Dress organization strike May 6, 1952 (item no.175) (Box 14, Folder 175)
  May 6th
- Dress organization strike May 21, 1952 (P) (item no.176) (Box 14, Folder 176)
  May 21th
- Dress strike picket line May 28th, 1952. (P) (item no.177) (Box 14, Folder 177)
- Freydberg strike 9/17/54 (item no.178), 1954 (Box 14, Folder 178)
  September 17th
- Freydberg strike Virginia March 1954. (P) (item no.179) (Box 14, Folder 179)
- Serbin strike New York office. 4/22/1955. (P) (item no.180) (Box 14, Folder 180)
- Northeast Department strike Philis Mays. June 1955 (P) (item no.181) (Box 14, Folder 181)
- E.O.T. strike Lancaster, Pennsylvania. August 1955. (P) (item no.182) (Box 14, Folder 182)
  Augsust
- Serbin of Miami Strike August 20th, 1955 (P) (item no.183) (Box 14, Folder 183)
  August 20th
- Northeast Department strike Vogue Lingerie, 148 Madison Avenue shop in Pennsylvania, 9/19/57. (P) (item no.184) (Box 14, Folder 184)